heatpressnation.com 2019-02-15

# Privacy Policy

Enetshops, LLC ("Enetshops, LLC") respects your privacy, and we are committed to protecting it. Please read this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to learn more about the manner in which we collect and use information that is generated when you visit www.heatpressnation.com and its affiliated sites (the "Site").

If you visit the Site and/or choose to create an account and/or place an order with us, we have designed our system to protect your privacy. Our system will be able to ascertain your geographic location from your IP (Internet Protocol) address, but we do not collect e-mail addresses or track the sites that you access while you use our services unless (i) we are required to do so by law; (ii) we have reason to believe that you have violated the terms and conditions of the Enetshops, LLC. Terms of Use; (iii) you have caused or attempted to cause harm to us or the other users of our Site; and/or (iv) you voluntarily provide us with personal information (as described below).

Two types of information may be collected when you visit our Site:

**Personal information** (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, password, or credit card information), which is only collected by us if you voluntarily submit it to us. For example, if you voluntarily place an order on the Site, we use the information we collect to confirm and process your order, to keep you updated on the status of your order, and to respond to any questions you may have. If you voluntarily create an account with us on our Site, we will receive the account information you submit so that we may better ensure that you receive streamlined service, special discounts, faster checkout, order history, and other products, information and/or services you requested. Where required, we also share this information with certain intermediaries (such as freight carriers, shipping companies and product manufacturers) to process and ship your order.

**Aggregate information** (such as log files/information about how many visitors log on to the Site and other non-identifying statistics), which is automatically collected from your use of the Site. Our servers will log IP addresses and collect third-party sites (and information from these sites) from your use of the Site. Enetshops, LLC. uses this information to measure the use of our Site, to improve the content of our Site, and to provide our users with the best possible services. Our Site may also use your IP address to help identify you and your shopping cart.

In sum, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself. However, you can, if you choose, participate in additional secured applications. For access to these applications, you are required to create an account with us or provide personal information when placing an order. If you place an order and/or create an account with us, we may also, from time to time, send you information about special offers, new products and services, system changes, and other information we think may be of interest. If for any reason you do not wish to receive this information, you may reply to any of our e-mails and type "unsubscribe" in the subject line or send an e-mail to our customer service e-mail to opt out. You may opt out of receiving future e-mails at any time.

Enetshops, LLC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide services that you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

We may transfer information about you if Enetshops, LLC. is acquired by or merged with another organization. In this event, Enetshops, LLC. will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share information gleaned from your use of the Site or the purchases you make with companies with whom we have marketing or other business relationships.

We share information with certain intermediaries (such as freight carriers, shipping companies and product manufacturers) where required to process and ship your order.

**"E-mail to a Friend" Feature**

There are several "e-mail to a friend" features on our Site that allow you to easily share product or other valuable information with your friends and family. Any e-mail addresses provided to us in the use of these features are used solely for direction of the e-mail communications. These e-mail addresses are not retained in our database, nor are they used for any communication other than the purposes for which they are originally solicited.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and ordering history. We work with third-party companies who may place cookies and/or web beacons/pixel tags (collectively "cookies") on your web browser. These cookies collect information that educates us on such things as how you navigate around our site, what products you browse and what products you purchase. This information allows us to better understand how you use our websites and how we can better serve your interests and provide you with better and more personalized product offerings. Generally, the information we collect using cookies does not identify you personally.

You may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete cookies as soon as you leave our sites. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit our sites, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this site. If you would like to place an order on our sites but object to or are otherwise unable to use cookies, please feel free to place your order via our toll-free number: 1-888-880-4884.

**Links to Other Sites**

We provide links to a number of third-party external sites. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of the external site company, its Website or Websites, or the products or services it promotes or sells. When you leave our Site to visit one of these linked sites, the only information transferred to the third party is the fact that you came from our Site.

Enetshops, LLC. is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of these third-party Websites. You should consult the privacy policies at these Websites to determine how your information may be used.

**Data Security**

Enetshops, LLC is committed to online data security, and for that reason we take steps to make all information received from you online as secure as reasonably possible from unauthorized access and use. We utilize a firewall, and our secure server software uses industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. SSL encodes your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, as it travels over the Internet so that all transactions are secure.

Please note that unauthorized access of our Site is prohibited and punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

**Children's Privacy**

We believe that protecting the privacy of children is especially important, and for that reason it is our intention to never collect or maintain information from children at our Site unless the disclosure of such information is done with verifiable parental or guardian consent.

**Your Consent**

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.

**Modifications**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy in whole or in part, we will post a notice on our Site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice and will apply to all users of our Site.

Should you have any questions or concerns about our shipping policy, please contact us.
